var questionsArr = [
    {
        question: 'Camels have three sets of eyelids.',
        answer: true
    },

    {
        question: 'A group of monkeys is called a herd.',
        answer: false
    },

    {
        question: 'Crocodiles shed tears when they eat food.',
        answer: true
    },

    {
        question: 'Sharks are mammals.',
        answer: false
    },

    {
        question: 'Sloths take two weeks to digest food.',
        answer: true
    },

    {
        question: 'A group of jellyfish is called a smack.',
        answer: true
    },

    {
        question: 'Spiders have five legs.',
        answer: false
    },

    {
        question: 'The German shepherd is a breed of cat.',
        answer: false
    },

    {
        question: 'Sea otters have favourite rocks that they use to crack open their food.',
        answer: true
    },

    {
        question: 'A penguin is in the same scientific family as a lobster.',
        answer: false
    }

]